[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "What's the name of the skyscraper in Die Hard?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Naturo Highrise",
      "Empire State Building",
      "Sony Headquarters"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Nakatomi Plaza"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "For what movie did Steven Spielberg win his first Oscar for Best Director?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Saving Private Ryan",
      "Lincoln",
      "Raiders of the Lost Ark"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Schindler's List"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "Who is the only actor to receive an Oscar nomination for acting in a Lord of the Rings movie?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sean Bean",
      "Andy Serkis",
      "Elijah Wood"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Ian Mckellen"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "Who wrote the theme music from Halloween?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Doe",
      "John Denver",
      "John Lennon"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "John Carpenter"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "What is the name of Quint's shark-hunting boat in Jaws?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Two Ladies from Spain",
      "The Doll's Eyes",
      "The White Whale"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Orca"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "In the action thriller Speed, why is Annie (Sandra Bullock)'s driver's license suspended?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Reckless Driving",
      "Rolling Stop",
      "Illegal Turn"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Speeding"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "The Battle of Thermopylae served as the basis of what highly stylized 2006 action flick?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Meet the Spartans",
      "Movie 42",
      "Rocky"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "300"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for Rocky?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bullwinkle",
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Sylvester Stallone"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "What is the real name of Uma Thurman's 'The Bride' character from Kill Bill?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Luna Lovegood",
      "Katherine Banks",
      "Lady Death"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Beatrix Kiddo"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "How many suns does Luke's home planet of Tatooine have in Star Wars?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1",
      "30",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "question": "What Martin Scorsese movie holds the record for F-bombs?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Taxi Driver",
      "Hugo",
      "The Irishman"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Wolf of Wall Street"
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "question": "What is the highest grossing horror of all time?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Us",
      "The Sixth Sense",
      "Ghostbusters"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "It"
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "question": "In what movie did Bill Paxton's character cry out 'Game over man, game over'!",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tombstone",
      "Nightcrawler",
      "Twister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Aliens"
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "question": "In what movie did Bruce Campbell's character say 'Alright you primitive screwheads, listen up! See this? This\u00e2\u20ac\u00a6 is my boomstick!'",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spider Man 2",
      "Bubba Ho-Tep",
      "Darkman"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Evil Dead: Army of Darkness"
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "question": "Freddy Krueger wears a striped sweater of what two colors?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blue and Red",
      "Purple and Yellow",
      "Orange and Black"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Red and Green"
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "question": "If you were to watch the Marvel movies in chronological order, which one would you start with?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Iron Man",
      "Black Panther",
      "Captain Marvel"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Captain America"
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "question": "The dog in The Sandlot's nickname is The Beast. What is its real name?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Slobberboy",
      "Tiamat",
      "Homer"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Hercules"
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "question": "Which professional athlete was considered for the lead in The Terminator?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike Tyson",
      "Tom Brady",
      "Wayne Gretzky"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "O.J Simpson"
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "question": "What are the names of Hades' minions in Hercules?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Greed and Sloth",
      "Muck and Mayhem",
      "Grease and Wheel"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Pain and Panic"
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "question": "What was the first Pixar movie?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Finding Nemo",
      "A Bug's Life",
      "Monsters, INC."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Toy Story"
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "question": "Emperor Kuzco turns into what animal in The Emperor's New Groove?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bat",
      "Horse",
      "Panther"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Llama"
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "question": "What is the most toxic and deadly thing in Monster's, Inc. ?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Love",
      "A Sock",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A Child"
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "question": "Which professional athlete was considered for the lead in The Terminator?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike Tyson",
      "Tom Brady",
      "Wayne Gretzky"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "O.J Simpson"
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "question": "What are the names of Hades' minions in Hercules?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Greed and Sloth",
      "Muck and Mayhem",
      "Grease and Wheel"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Pain and Panic"
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "question": "What was the first Pixar movie?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Finding Nemo",
      "A Bug's Life",
      "Monsters, INC."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Toy Story"
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "question": "Emperor Kuzco turns into what animal in The Emperor's New Groove?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bat",
      "Horse",
      "Panther"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Llama"
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "question": "Who was the first cartoon character to get a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bugs Bunny",
      "Optimus Prime",
      "Jessica Rabbit"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Mickey Mouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "question": "What is the most toxic and deadly thing in Monster's, Inc. ?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Love",
      "A Sock",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A Child"
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "question": "Michael Myer's mask in Halloween is of what actor's face?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bob Marley",
      "Steve Jobs",
      "Clint Eastwood"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "William Shatner"
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "question": "How many people does John Wick kill in John Wick?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "35",
      "57",
      "42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "77"
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "question": "What role did Kurt Russel turn down to play as Jack Burton in Big Trouble in Little China?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soldier",
      "Hateful 8",
      "Deathproof"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Highlander"
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "question": "What is the name of Jack Burton's truck in Big Trouble in Little China?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lady in Red",
      "Smashburger",
      "Sub's Tubs"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Porkchop Express"
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "question": "What movie had Adam Sandler's character marrying that of Drew Barrymore?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "50 First Dates",
      "Click",
      "Little Nicky"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Wedding Singer"
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "question": "What South Korean thriller won an Academy Award for Best Picture, Best Directing, and Best Writing?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Host",
      "Teeth",
      "Okja"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Parasite"
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "question": "What actor got his first major role in A Nightmare On Elm Street?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Billy Bob Thorton",
      "Jason Momoa",
      "Guy Ritchie"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Johnny Depp"
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "question": "How many movies does the MCU have?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "20",
      "12",
      "45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "question": "What day is Harry Potter's birthday?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "March 3, 1982",
      "October 3, 1986",
      "November 20, 1981"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "July 31, 1980"
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "question": "What movie had costars Nicolas Cage, John Cusack, and John Malkovich?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gone in 60 Seconds",
      "The Rock",
      "Raising Arizona"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Con Air"
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "question": "Which Disney character appeared in Frozen as a stuffed animal?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Goofy",
      "Ariel",
      "Mulan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Mickey Mouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "question": "What actress has won the most Academy Awards?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Glenn Close",
      "Isabella Rossellini",
      "Betty White"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Katherine Hepburn"
  },
  {
    "id": "41",
    "question": "Where was the Lord of the Rings trilogy filmed?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Germany",
      "Australia",
      "Ireland"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "question": "Who directed the film Psycho?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven King",
      "John Carpenter",
      "Lewis Carol"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Alfred Hitchcock"
  },
  {
    "id": "43",
    "question": "What film is the line, 'Frankly Scarlet, I don't give a damn' from?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Casablanca",
      "The Postman Always Rings Twice",
      "The Sound of Music"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Gone with the Wind"
  },
  {
    "id": "44",
    "question": "What is the name of Thor's Axe in the Marvel Universe?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Face Smasher",
      "Ground Cleaver",
      "Titan's Bane"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Storm Breaker"
  },
  {
    "id": "45",
    "question": "What was the name of Max's love interest in A Goofy Movie?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rachel",
      "Rose",
      "River"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Roxanne"
  },
  {
    "id": "46",
    "question": "What illegal activity was Hiro participating in at the beginning of Big Hero 6?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gambling",
      "Racing",
      "Vandalizing Property"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Robot Fighting"
  },
  {
    "id": "47",
    "question": "In The movie Pacific Rim, how many Kaiju kills does Striker Eureka have?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "48",
    "question": "What is Gohan's Dragon's name in Dragon Ball Z?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Turtles",
      "Porunga",
      "Daelgus"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Icarus"
  },
  {
    "id": "49",
    "question": "What is Bulma's last name in Dragon Ball?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boxers",
      "Capsule",
      "Lace"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Briefs"
  },
  {
    "id": "50",
    "question": "What are the names of the Aliens on fake planet Namek in Dragon Ball Z?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cui and Pui Pui",
      "Dora and Neiz",
      "Rildo and Drildo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Zaccro and Raiti"
  },
  {
    "id": "51",
    "question": "Which one of these is not a member of Garlic Jr's 'spice boys'?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salt",
      "Vinegar",
      "Mustard"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Pepper"
  },
  {
    "id": "52",
    "question": "How did Lelouch come up with the name Lamperouge in Code Geass?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "It was inspired by Suzaku",
      "He made it up",
      "The Ashford family gave it to him"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "It was his mother's maiden name"
  },
  {
    "id": "53",
    "question": "Who rescued Princess Cornelia at Narita from Kallen and Zero in Code Geass?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Andreas Dalton",
      "Jeremiah Gottwald",
      "Gilbert Guilford"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Suzaku Kururugi"
  },
  {
    "id": "54",
    "question": "While Lelouch was at the Chinese Federation in the episode Power of Passion, who impersonated Lelouch at Ashford Academy in Code Geass?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peco",
      "Suzaku",
      "Kallen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Sayoko"
  },
  {
    "id": "55",
    "question": "Which Ashford Academy student council member was one of the terrorists Lelouch helped in Shinjuku in Code Geass?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mao",
      "Anya",
      "Gino"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Kallen"
  },
  {
    "id": "56",
    "question": "Which one of these Nightmares is considered to be Generation 6?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gekka",
      "MR-1",
      "Burai"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Gawain"
  },
  {
    "id": "57",
    "question": "From Austin Powers Finish this line\u00e2\u20ac\u00a6'Don't worry, things won't get\u00e2\u20ac\u00a6'",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freaky",
      "Kinky",
      "Tantric"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Weird"
  },
  {
    "id": "58",
    "question": "In the Matrix, what color pill does Neo take?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blue",
      "Green",
      "Orange"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Red"
  },
  {
    "id": "59",
    "question": "In To Kill A Mockingbird what is the name of Scout's father?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jim",
      "Paul",
      "George"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Atticus"
  },
  {
    "id": "60",
    "question": "Finish the line\u00e2\u20ac\u00a6 'Austin, I am your\u00e2\u20ac\u00a6'",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brother",
      "Uncle",
      "Mother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "id": "61",
    "question": "For what movie did Tom Hanks score his first Academy Award nomination?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Forrest Gump",
      "You've got Mail",
      "Toy Story"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Big"
  },
  {
    "id": "62",
    "question": "In Ready Player One what is the name of the program the whole planet logs into daily?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Simulation Nation",
      "Facebook",
      "Parcival's Paradise"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Oasis"
  },
  {
    "id": "63",
    "question": "What American writer/director starred in several iconic European-produced Spaghetti Westerns?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Wayne",
      "George Clooney",
      "Jeff Bridges"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Clint Eastwood"
  },
  {
    "id": "64",
    "question": "Who is the highest grossing director of all time?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Quentin Tarantino",
      "Christopher Nolan",
      "James Cameron"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg"
  },
  {
    "id": "65",
    "question": "In Terminator 2, what is the license plate of the motorcycle the terminator used to rescue John Conner?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "9J4KJ2",
      "9YT635",
      "9MY763"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9A7218"
  },
  {
    "id": "66",
    "question": "In Ternimator, Who is John Conner's Father?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anton Yelchin",
      "Bryan Prince",
      "Patrick Smith"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Kyle Reese"
  },
  {
    "id": "67",
    "question": "What actor plays Rex in We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story?",
    "ncorrectAnswers": [
      "Joey Shea",
      "Jay Leno",
      "Martin Short"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "John Goodman"
  },
  {
    "id": "68",
    "question": "In Back to the Future 2, what prediction about the future did they get correctly?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "People walk around with their pockets out",
      "Holographic projections",
      "Self tying shoes"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Flat screen TVs"
  },
  {
    "id": "69",
    "question": "In Pacific Rim, what mark model is Gypsy Danger?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "70",
    "question": "In Transformers, how many years was the Ark on Earth before it was rediscovered by humans?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "3 million years",
      "5 million years",
      "6 million years"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4 million years"
  },
  {
    "id": "71",
    "question": "In Tron, how does the original creator of the digital frontier refer to his computer creation?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Forest",
      "The Path",
      "The Room"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Grid"
  },
  {
    "id": "72",
    "question": "In Tron: Legacy what character does Jeff Bridges play? ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sam Flynn",
      "Zuse",
      "Dumont"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Kevin Flynn"
  },
  {
    "id": "73",
    "question": "What score did John Williams NOT compose?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Star Wars",
      "Harry Potter",
      "Jurassic Park"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Pirates of the Caribbean"
  },
  {
    "id": "74",
    "question": " In Lord of the rings, Frodo was given a blade that would glow when what creature is nearby?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elves",
      "Ents",
      "Dragons"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Orcs"
  },
  {
    "id": "75",
    "question": "In Lord of the rings, what is the Elvish word for friend?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ada",
      "Coron",
      "Ered"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Mellon"
  },
  {
    "id": "76",
    "question": "In Lord of the Rings, what is the name of Gandalf's sword? ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Orcbane",
      "Stabby McStabstab",
      "Harpe"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Foehammer"
  },
  {
    "id": "77",
    "question": "Who was the first person to turn into a monster in The Thing(probably)?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blair",
      "Cooper",
      "Windows"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Norris"
  },
  {
    "id": "78",
    "question": "What year is Ready Player One based in?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1985",
      "1998",
      "2012"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2045"
  },
  {
    "id": "79",
    "question": " In Star Wars, what is the Chewbacca home planet?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Endor",
      "Tatooine",
      "Dagobah"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Kashyyyk"
  },
  {
    "id": "80",
    "question": "In Star Wars, who killed Jabba the Hutt?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Luke Skywalker",
      "Han Solo",
      "Himself"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Leia Organa"
  },
  {
    "id": "81",
    "question": "Who DID NOT direct a star wars movie?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "JJ Abrams",
      "Rian Johnson",
      "George Lucas"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg"
  },
  {
    "id": "82",
    "question": "In Spirited Away, what is the name of the spirit who is transformed into a mouse and helps Chihiro in the bathhouse?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "No-Face",
      "Kamaji",
      "Bah"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Boh"
  },
  {
    "id": "83",
    "question": "What is the name of the main character in Only Yesterday?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Teko",
      "Yuuko",
      "Miki"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Taeko"
  },
  {
    "id": "84",
    "question": "In Ponyo on the Cliff by the Sea, what is the name of the sea goddess who transforms into a human girl and becomes friends with Sosuke?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Taeko",
      "Lisa",
      "Fujimoto"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Ponyo"
  },
  {
    "id": "85",
    "question": "In Kiki's Delivery Service, what is the name of Kiki's black cat?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joji",
      "Duke",
      "The Baron"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Jiji"
  },
  {
    "id": "86",
    "question": "In Howl's Moving Castle, what is the name of the fire demon who provides power for Howl's moving castle?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lucifer",
      "Turnip Head",
      "The Witch of the Waste"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Calcifer"
  },
  {
    "id": "87",
    "question": "In the film Porco Rosso, what is the name of the seaplane pilot who befriends Porco?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gio",
      "Piccolo",
      "Curtis"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Fio"
  },
  {
    "id": "88",
    "question": "In The Tale of Princess Kaguya, what is the name of the emperor who wants to make Princess Kaguya his bride?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sakura",
      "Miyatsuko",
      "Okina"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Emperor"
  },
  {
    "id": "89",
    "question": "What is the name of the hotel in The Shining?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Stanley",
      "The Rosedale",
      "Hotel Transylvania"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Overlook"
  },
  {
    "id": "90",
    "question": "Who directed the movie Psycho?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stanley Kubrick",
      "Roman Polanski",
      "John Lenon"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Alfred Hitchcock"
  },
  {
    "id": "91",
    "question": "What is the name of the haunted house in The Amityville Horror?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "7 Ocean Avenue",
      "42 Ocean Avenue",
      "Oceans 8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "112 Ocean Avenue"
  },
  {
    "id": "92",
    "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in Nightmare on Elm Street?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freddy Krueger",
      "Tina Gray",
      "Freddy Mercury"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Nancy Thompson"
  },
  {
    "id": "93",
    "question": "Who directed the movie The Texas Chainsaw Massacre?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wes Craven",
      "John Carpenter",
      "John Wayne's Booth"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Tobe Hooper"
  },
  {
    "id": "94",
    "question": "What is the name of the ghost in The Ring?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sadako",
      "Mariko",
      "Kirby"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Samara"
  },
  {
    "id": "95",
    "question": "Who directed the movie Halloween?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tobe Hooper",
      "Wes Craven",
      "John Hopkins"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "John Carpenter"
  },
  {
    "id": "96",
    "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in Scream?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Billy Loomis",
      "Stu Macher",
      "Ashley Tisdale"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Sidney Prescott"
  },
  {
    "id": "97",
    "question": "Who directed the movie Psycho?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Roman Polanski",
      "David Lynch",
      "Martin Scorsese"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Alfred Hitchcock"
  },
  {
    "id": "98",
    "question": " What is the name of the protagonist in The Exorcist?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Regan MacNeil",
      "Chris MacNeil",
      "Sharon Spencer"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Regan MacNeil "
  },
  {
    "id": "99",
    "question": "Who created the character of Iron Man?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jack Kirby",
      "Steve Ditko",
      "Bruce Lee"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Stan Lee"
  },
  {
    "id": "100",
    "question": "What is the real name of the character Deadpool?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peter Parker",
      "Scott Summers",
      "Victor Creed"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Wade Wilson"
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "question": "Who played Thor in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chris Evans",
      "Robert Downey Jr.",
      "Mark Ruffalo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Hemsworth"
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "question": "What was the first Marvel film to be produced independently, outside of the Marvel Studios banner?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "X-Men (2000)",
      "Spider-Man (2002)",
      "Cocaine Bear (2023)"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Blade (1998) "
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "question": "What is Captain America's shield made of?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steel",
      "Jelly Beans",
      "Uru"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Vibranium"
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "question": "What is the real name of the character The Hulk?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bill Gates",
      "Dr. Phil",
      "Bill Clinton"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Bruce Banner"
  },
  {
    "id": "105",
    "question": "In what year was the Avengers film released?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2010",
      "2014",
      "2016"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2012"
  },
  {
    "id": "106",
    "question": "Who played the villain Thanos in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Josh Elder",
      "Tom Hiddleston",
      "Idris Elba"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Josh Brolin"
  },
  {
    "id": "107",
    "question": "What is the name of the Infinity Stone that is associated with reality?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Power Stone",
      "Time Stone",
      "Soul Stone"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Reality Stone"
  },
  {
    "id": "108",
    "question": "In Tron: Legacy, where is the entrance to the digital world found?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "At a library",
      "In a zoo",
      "In a bathroom"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "In an arcade"
  }
]